Daniel Clement

Full-Stack Software Engineer / Web Developer

3103 Helena Springs Way, Apt C Augusta, GA 30909 (805) 574-9557

dnlclmnt@gmail.com | github.com/dnlclmnt | linkedin.com/in/danielclement-/

Profile

Highly motivated software developer looking to transition from a certified pharmacy technician with over 6 years of experience. Acclimated with fast-paced environments and quick-learning with experience in full-stack development. Dedicated to process improvement and has a keen aptitude for critical thinking and problem-solving. Also served as supply manager, equipment manager, and customer service representative in respective workplaces.

Technical Skills

 Technologies: JavaScript, HTML, CSS, React, Ruby, Rails, RSpec, Jest, Postman, PostgreSQL, Git, GitHub, MySQL

Other Skills

- Team-player
- Problem-solving
- Inventory management and procurement
- Excellent patient/ customer care interaction
- Accountability and high attention to detail
- Team management and training
- Strong verbal and written communication

Experience

AUG 2022 - NOV 2022

LEARN Academy - Full Stack Web Developer Training

- Completed over 640 hours of coding experience, with three months of coding curriculum in solo, pair programming, and mob programming environments, as well as a one month remote internship to utilize skillset.
- Gained a solid proficiency of fundamental JavaScript, Ruby, and Rails knowledge, as well as exposure to test-driven-development and full-stack application development.

APR 2021- FEB 2022

Augusta University Medical Center, Augusta, GA - Clinical Research Pharmacy Technician

Provide technical and administrative support for the pharmacy component of clinical research
protocols safely, efficiently and in adherence with Good Clinical Research Practices (GCP) as well as
state/Federal law, health-system policies and procedures, applicable standards, and pharmacy best
practices.

- Created several processes for organization of clinical research inventory and archival of studies.
- Assisted study coordinators with inquiries, audits, and documentation gathering/correction.

MAR 2015 - JUN 2017

Naval Branch Health Clinic Port Hueneme, Port Hueneme, CA - Pharmacy Technician

- Recouped \$13,667 through the expired medication program.
- Proficiency in pharmacy operations contributed to the processing of over 30,000 prescriptions.

MAR 2013 - MAR 2015

Naval Hospital Naples, Naples, Italy - Pharmacy Technician

- Managed a \$2.3M annual budget for the ordering and receipting of pharmaceuticals.
- Reorganized pharmacy and implemented bar-code tracking system for faster supply ordering.
- Patient contact representative for department, resulting in 93% customer satisfaction rate.

Education

AUG 2022 - NOV 2022

LEARN Academy, Remote

Full-Stack Software Engineering

OCT 2018 - JUN 2020

Augusta Technical College, Augusta, GA 30909

Computer Programming

APR 2012 - MAR 2013

Medical Education and Training Campus, Fort Sam Houston, TX

Hospital Corpsman/Pharmacy Technician Training

FEB 2012 - APR 2012

US Navy Boot Camp Recruit Training Command, Great Lakes, IL